## MOSCOL SUAREZ, ADRIAN GABRIEL UPC-COMPUTER SCIENCE

Lima - Lima - Perú Phone: +51 996 571 206

Email: adriangmoscols@gmail.com

ID: 70350368

Graduate of the Computer Science program at the Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas (UPC). Notable for active communication and leadership in group projects. Interested in web development areas with Full-Stack experience, JavaScript, and Spring Boot framework for backend development, and Angular, Vue, and React frameworks for frontend development. Additionally, keen on Data Science and Data Engineering for data preprocessing and analysis using R or Python and Power BI. Furthermore, committed to continuous improvement for the benefit of the company and its environment through the achievement of timely objectives.

Work Experience:

08/01/2023 - Present MEDIA LAB TECH S.A.C.

Activity: Análisis de datos Position: Professional Trainee

Responsibilities: Data cleaning and analysis for client companies.

12/14/2022 - 02/28/2023 **OPPORTUNITY EMPRESAS SAC** 

Activity: FullStack Developer Position: Programmer Analyst

Responsibilities: Fullstack development of websites for companies.

Achievements: Successfully accomplished all proposed projects within defined deadlines.

02/14/2022 - 05/14/2022 **EVOL - TSnet S.A.** 

Activity: IT Services Consultant at Oracle

Position: Intern

Responsibilities: Development of integrations and reports for projects, as well as documentation of

he same

Achievements: Successful deployment of QUICORP's enterprise projects through project

development.

**Education:** 

2018 - 2023 Peruvian University of Applied Sciences, Perú

Computer Science Graduate with 100.0% academic progress

2012 - 2017 San Ignacio de Recalde School, Perú

School High School

**Courses and Seminars:** 

Ago 2023 - Present The Complet 2023 Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 Machine Learning

upc

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021 Master en Frameworks JavaScript: Aprende Angular, React, Vue

Udemy

Mar 2020 - Jul 2020 Desarrollo Web

upc

Languag

es: English - Advanced Written - Technical

spoken

Portuguese - Basic Written - Basic Spoken French - Basic Written - Basic Spoken

Spanish - Native Speaker

**Computer Skills:** 

Full-Stack Development (Intermediate)

SQL 2019 (Intermediate)

PYTHON: PROGRAMMING AND DATA ANALYSIS (Intermediate)

Machine Learning (Basic)

C, C++, Visual C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SASS (Intermediate)

R - Studio (Basic)

Java, Spring Boot (Basic) Nodee.js (Intermediate)

JAVA 8 (Basic)

Neural Networks and Deep Learning (Basic)

Excel (Advanced)

Power Bi (Intermediate)

Alteryx (Basic)